It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King.
and he became a legend.
This is the Black Market.
It's a bit dangerous. but they have
some very effective magical items.
Damn it. I lost again! Bah-ha...
I can see the future.
That old lady's good.
I really shouldn't be
wasting time here. anyway.
Hey. she's cute!
Bah-ha!
The Black Market is no place
for you lovely ladies. Bah-ha!
Get lost. you insect.
Bah-ha...
Hey! I found something really cool!
Bah-ha!
Th-That's...
Huh? Hey. you're Bah-ha!
It's Sekke! Bah-ha!
How've you been. Bah-ha?
The name's Bah-ha! No. wait. Sekke!
Who's that?
I took the Entrance Exam with him.
Ah. you're a member of the
Green Praying Mantises.
He's with two beautiful girls?! Wait. no...
They're both members of
the Black Bulls. too.
Asta. you bastard!
You're making me jealous.
Besides. it's all your fault that
I ended up in the Green Praying Mantises.
Bah-ha! You infuriating bah-hastard!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
The Wizard King Saw
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know. yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go. though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide. I never give up
To faraway future. I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had. so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
Are you out shopping with these girls?
Well. today's our day off.
Bah-ha! Must be nice.
Even if it's your day off. shouldn't
you be finding some basic tasks
to do for points.
instead of messing around?
I heard the Black Bulls
have negative stars—
Stars! Oh. yeah! Listen to this!
We got a star from the
Wizard King on our first mission!
What?! You can't be serious!
Well done. you two.
They're serious?!
Calm down. me.
Bah-ha. bah-ha...
I-I see! Seems like you're working hard.
What about you. Bah-ha?
It's Sekke!
W-Well. I... The other day...
I-I got my second star...
Th-Thief!
My winnings! Stop!
That old lady...
He's got some nerve.
stealing in front of Magic Knights.
No kidding. But everything will be
fine if we leave it to the little boy.
I'm counting on you.
Bah-ha!
I'm not going to let you
steal all the glory. Asta!
Bronze Creation Magic: Sekke Shooting Star!
Lame!
Gross!
Leave this to me. You lovely ladies
can go relax with that old lady.
Ew!
No!
Bah-ha!
Hold it!
Just try and catch me.
Stop. dang it!
What the...
Sorry!
I finally lost him.
Not yet!
He's so damn persistent!
I-I can't see!
I'm not letting you get away!
How is he catching up to me
when he's only running?
I have to do something about that cloud.
or I'll never catch up.
If it's a cloud created by magic...
Right!
Do you actually think you can cut
through my Bandit's Cloud Wind—
What?!
You're not getting away!
Bah-ha!
I'm going to take the glory on this one!
That's awesome!
Bah-ha!
Bah-ha! You're under arrest!
He's my prey! Bah-hahaha!
Bah-hahaha... huh?
Bah-ha?
That's...
Knock off that stupid laugh of yours!
I'm taking you down with me...
What's wrong. Bah-ha?
Poison... Poison's coursing through me.
Hang in there. Bah-ha!
Bah... ha...
Am I going to die?
Now that I think about it. I was
once trying to get to the top. too...
Bah-ha!
I hate that I have to leave
everything to him. but...
You're the man who defeated me.
Make it all the way to the
top for my sake. too.
I'm leaving my dream to you!
Bah-ha...
Bah-haha...
I guess going out like this isn't so bad.
Bah... ha...
Bah-ha! Bah-ha!
Huh? I'm not dying?
Bah-ha?!
Wh-What are you—
Don't leave something so important with me!
Survive and make your own dream come true!
Don't give up. you idiot!
Come on. There's no way this would kill you.
Bah-ha?
It's just a momentary numbing poison.
Put this Shique ointment on it.
and you'll be better in no time.
Bah-ha! Make sure you stay diligent
until the next time I see you. Asta!
See ya. bah-ha!
See ya. Bah-ha!
On the outside. our little boy
definitely looks younger than him.
but it seems our little boy is
much stronger on the inside.
Don't let it get taken again. ma'am.
Thank you. Magic Knights.
See ya. ma'am.
Be careful.
Live a long. happy life.
Magic negation. eh?
That's a type of magic
I've never seen before.
Actually... is that even magic?
Yami sure took in an interesting kid.
This is why I can't stop
wandering around in disguise.
I finally found you!
Uh-oh...
What in the world are you doing. Wizard King?
28th Wizard King
Julius Novachrono
What am I doing? I'm strolling through
the castle town looking for new magic.
What?! Have you any
awareness of your position?!
Encounters with magic are once in a lifetime.
That doesn't—
You never know what kind of magic
you're going to encounter and where.
Listen to me. you magic nerd!
Now. now. calm down. Marx.
Isn't that the new kid from William's squad?
Well. I'm off to encounter even
more new magic. I'll be back later.
Wait. damn it!
Member of the Golden Dawn
Klaus Lunettes
The Golden Dawn's new recruit. Yuno...
Member of the Golden Dawn
Yuno
The candidate that every Magic Knight
Captain wanted at the Entrance Exam.
Member of the Golden Dawn
Mimosa Vermillion
And then we have the other new recruit.
Mimosa Vermillion. from the royal family.
Their first mission is...
to act as bodyguards
for Salim de Hapshass.
We are to escort the son of Hapshass.
who serves in the House of Lords.
to our ally. the Heart Kingdom?
You know who Lord Hapshass is. don't you?
I know his name.
I've only heard negative things about him.
such as that he's new money.
I'm sure that's why he's worried that his son.
who is going to study in the Heart Kingdom.
might be attacked by bandits on the way.
But there are many powerful mages
among the lord's family...
Apparently. he feels having Magic Knights
act as his bodyguards will be safer.
Lord Hapshass makes very generous
donations to the Magic Knights every year.
so it's rather hard to decline.
Do you object?
N-No!
We need to accept every kind of mission.
That will also benefit the Clover Kingdom.
Yes. sir. I am aware of that.
Take Mimosa with you. too.
I'm sure with you along as their mentor.
they'll be more than enough.
I'm counting on you to
look after the new recruits.
Salim de Hapshass lost to Yuno in the final
part of the Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
He ended up being unable
to join the Magic Knights.
So why was Yuno appointed
as one of his bodyguards?
My first mission... I'm so nervous.
Klaus. Yuno. it's a
pleasure to work with you.
Yeah.
Don't let your guard down. Mimosa.
Y-Yes. sir.
That goes for you. too.
I know.
You insolent newbie.
How have you been. Yuno?
Don't look so scary.
I requested you as my bodyguard
because I want to apologize.
I hear that you intend to
become the Wizard King.
How did you know?
You were chosen by all of the captains.
You could've joined any squad.
and you ended up choosing the
Golden Dawn. so I had a feeling.
The more you achieve from now on.
the more your name will spread
throughout the kingdom...
Yuno. the one who bears the
four-leaf clover grimoire.
Make sure your dream of becoming
the Wizard King comes true.
And then I'll be able to
brag to my future children
that I once fought the Wizard King.
And then they'll say. "Daddy. you're so cool!"
We have some time before we
get to the Heart Kingdom.
Could you tell me a little
more about yourself?
I won't pester you if you're not up for it.
I'm from Hage Village.
I've heard of it. It's a village
in the Forsaken Realm. isn't it?
I think that's where the legend
of the first Wizard King
who defeated the demons comes from.
It's not just a legend. A giant
demon skull is actually still there.
Oh?
Apparently. I was found abandoned in
front of a church when I was a baby.
I've never seen my parents.
and I have no idea who they are.
The church was very poor. but the father
and sister there took very good care of me.
I'm very grateful to them.
No problems so far.
but there must be someone
in the Hapshass family
who can use transportation magic.
How did we get stuck with this?
Not to mention. we're the only bodyguards.
If there was a real threat of an attack.
wouldn't they have more bodyguards?
There are too many unknowns on this mission.
Oh?
What's that?
Those clouds...
They're a little creepy.
I'll go check them out.
Hey! No one said you could—
Be on your guard. Mimosa.
Y-Yes. sir.
Yuno. protect the ship!
I intend to.
Go!
That was magnificent!
Were those men not after Salim?
You saved me back there. Well done. Yuno.
I didn't even have the opportunity
to use my Lightning God Rising Salim.
I'm even more interested in you now.
I know. Why don't you take me to your town?
I want to see the place where you were born.
I want to know where you had
to live to grow up so strong.
Lord Salim. that's rather out of the way.
Besides. given what just happened.
we don't know what else
might happen along the way.
so we should head straight
for the Heart Kingdom—
No matter who may come after me.
you three will protect me. won't you?
Well. yes. of course.
But for nobility to go to a peasant
village in the Forsaken Realm...
It'll just be a quick stop.
Right...
I'm sure Yuno would like to see
everyone back at his church. too. Right?
That's not your concern.
Now. now...
So that's the demon's skull!
It's quite big. And on top of it is
a statue of the first Wizard King.
I see. So where is this church?
There.
Oh?
Yuno!
Welcome back!
Thanks.
You've grown so much!
I haven't changed. It's only
been two months since I left.
Really? But... Yes. Your face has matured.
You look more like an adult.
What brings you here today?
We're stopping by briefly during our mission.
Why must I visit this village
in the Forsaken Realm?
Oh. um. hello. I'm Sister Lily.
I'm Klaus Lunettes of the honorable
Golden Dawn. led by William Vangeance.
I'm a mentor to these new recruits.
Hello. Klaus. Thank you
for looking after Yuno.
I've heard of you from Yuno's letters.
Letters?
What did you write about me?
Honestly...
I'm Mimosa Vermillion.
one of Yuno's colleagues.
I've heard of you. too. Mimosa.
Oh!
What did you write about me?
Ah. what a beauty.
Huh?
I am from Hapshass Village.
the son of Lord Hapshass and the heir to
the Hapshass family. Salim de Hapshass.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Oh. I-I'm so sorry! I just...
N-No. it's all right. Sister.
Yuno! It's Yuno!
How are you?!
Welcome back!
What are you doing here. Yuno?
Whoa. that robe's awesome!
That's the Golden Dawn's.
It's the real thing!
Yay. it's Yuno! Yay! Yay!
Yay!
Hey. where's Asta?
Where's Asta?
Are you keeping in contact with Asta?
No.
Are you staying the night tonight?
You are. right?
Um...
Unfortunately. we're just stopping by.
We have to hurry on our way.
Aww!
Now. now. we don't have
to be in such a hurry.
We can spare an hour or so.
But—
In that case. I'll prepare
some famous Hage tato dishes.
Yuno. stay and have some food.
That goes for all of you. Please. come in.
Wow. what a splendid church.
I've never seen such a
tiny church. It's so cute.
Tiny?!
It's like a playhouse.
Wha—
Yuno. tell us about the Magic Knights.
Yeah. tell us!
Us!
Why must I enter such a filthy little church?
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh. go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Sekke's Bah-ha Seminar! Part 2
Sekke's Bah-ha Seminar. Part 2!
We're still doing this?
But of course. Asta.
You haven't learned the
ways of bah-ha at all yet.
Your Shooting Star's pretty cool!
Ah. so you understand how grand it is!
That part in front is especially awesome!
Good. You are starting to
understand the ways of bah-ha!
I see. So that's bah-ha.
Yes. Starting today. you have attained bah-ha!
Bah-hahaha! Bah-hahaha!
Bah-hahaha!
Men are so stupid.
Curse that Yuno! He's so
insolent for a new recruit.
I'm your senior! If you don't listen to me.
you'll feel the wrath of my glasses!
Black Clover. Page 13:
"The Wizard King Saw. Continued."
Page 13
The Wizard King Saw. Continued
Not giving up is my magic!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm